. 。
.  。
Oh,
أوه،
-Show me the
-ارنى ال
ending. -Okay.
النهاية.  -تمام.
Let go of the last episode.
اترك الحلقة الاخيرة.
Mr. Leng returned the old mansion.
عاد السيد لينغ القصر القديم.
Miss Su's room
غرفة الآنسة سو
will be preserved forever.
سيتم الحفاظ عليها إلى الأبد.
Ouyang Yuchuan,
أويانغ يوتشوان ،
Bunny,
الأرنب
Mr. Ouyang.
السيد اويانغ.
Yes.
نعم.
Sir,
سيد،
you can't drink anymore.
لا يمكنك أن تشرب بعد الآن.
Uncle Wang.
العم وانغ.
What can we do if it goes on like this?
ماذا يمكننا أن نفعل إذا استمر الأمر على هذا النحو؟
Don't touch me!
لا تلمسني!
I'm not drunk.
أنا لست مخمورا.
I can't drink it anymore,
لا أستطيع أن أشربه بعد الآن ،
sir. Sir, listen to me.
سيد.  سيدي ، استمع إلي.
Get me another bottle.
أحضر لي زجاجة أخرى.
Okay. Come on.
تمام.  تعال.
Get up.
استيقظ.
Go to the sofa. Can you
اذهب إلى الأريكة.  هل تستطيع
get me a bottle of wine now?
أحضر لي زجاجة نبيذ الآن؟
Be good.
كن جيد.
Get me another bottle of wine.
أحضر لي زجاجة نبيذ أخرى.
Listen to me, sir.
استمع إلي يا سيدي.
I'm not drunk. I can't drink any more.
أنا لست مخمورا.  لا أستطيع أن أشرب أكثر.
Come on.
تعال.
Give me a cushion.
أعطني وسادة.
Little rabbit,
أرنب صغير
I'm coming.
أنا قادم.
Hi,
أهلاً،
What's your name?
ما اسمك؟
Bunny,
الأرنب
where are you?
أين أنت؟
I miss you.
أفتقدك.
You fool.
يالك من أحمق.
Ms. Su, I'm moved.
السيدة سو ، لقد تأثرت.
I don't like the ending.
لا أحب النهاية.
Let's call it a day.
دعونا نسميها اليوم.
Dismissed.
مرفوض.
Hi,
أهلاً،
Little rabbit.
أرنب صغير.
Let go of your incorrigible pride first.
تخلَّ عن كبريائك الذي لا يمكن إصلاحه أولاً.
Run to my warm arms.
اركض إلى ذراعي الدافئة.
Bunny,
الأرنب
aren't you happy to see me?
ألست سعيدا لرؤيتي
Ouyang Yuchuan,
أويانغ يوتشوان ،
why are you crying?
لماذا تبكين
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
Of course I'm here for you.
بالطبع أنا هنا من أجلك.
Let me see if it's true.
دعني أرى ما إذا كان هذا صحيحًا.
Little rabbit,
أرنب صغير
it really wasn't a dream.
حقا لم يكن حلما.
Are you ready to accept my exclusive favor?
هل أنت مستعد لقبول صالحي الحصري؟
Yeah
نعم
The heart of Stallone is indeed the heart of true love.
قلب ستالون هو في الواقع قلب الحب الحقيقي.
But the main idea is not to separate two people,
لكن الفكرة الرئيسية ليست الفصل بين شخصين ،
but to test their love.
ولكن لاختبار حبهم.